function qchage(x) {
  if (x == 0) {
    return htmlq = [
      {
        numn: 1,
        question: "HTML is what type of language?",
        answer: "B. Markup language.",
        options: [
          "A. Scripting language.",
          "B. Markup language.",
          "C. Programming language.",
          "D. Network protocol language.",
        ],
      },
      {
        numn: 2,
        question: "HTML uses which of the following?",
        answer: "C. Fixed tags defined by the language",
        options: [
          "A. User defined tags.",
          "B. Pre-specified tags.",
          "C. Fixed tags defined by the language",
          "D. Tags only for linking.",
        ],
      },
      {
        numn: 3,
        question: "The year in which HTML was created?",
        answer: "C. 1993",
        options: ["A. 1950", "B. 1999", "C. 1993", "D. 2002"],
      },
      {
        numn: 4,
        question:
          "A block level element of the HTML always starts with ________.",
        answer: "Markup language.",
        options: ["A. New window", "B. New line", "C. New page", "D. New tab"],
      },
      {
        numn: 5,
        question: "Which of the following is true about attributes?",
        answer: "B. Defines the element more",
        options: [
          "A. Applies changes to everything",
          "B. Defines the element more",
          "C. Allows for no changes to the site",
          "D. Gives structure and text",
        ],
      },
      {
        numn: 6,
        question:
          "Which of the following tags is used to define the caption of the table in HTML?",
        answer: "C. title",
        options: ["A. C", "B. tc", "C. title", "D. caption"],
      },
      {
        numn: 7,
        question: "You should save HTML files with which file extension?",
        answer: "D. .html",
        options: ["A. .htm", "B. .index", "C. .webpage", "D. .html"],
      },
      {
        numn: 8,
        question: "Which attribute is used to name an element uniquely?",
        answer: "A. id",
        options: ["A. id", "B. class", "C. name", "D. dot"],
      },
      {
        numn: 9,
        question:
          "Which of the following is the correct way to add background color in HTML?",
        answer: "D. < body style = “background-color: green;” >",
        options: [
          "A. < body color = “green” >",
          "B. < body bg-color = “green” >",
          "C. < body style = “background-color=green” >",
          "D. < body style = “background-color: green;” >",
        ],
      },
      {
        numn: 10,
        question:
          "Tags and texts that are not directly displayed on the page are written in which of the following tags.",
        answer: "A. head",
        options: ["A. head", "B. titel", "C. body", "D. html"],
      },
    ];
  }
  if (x==1) {
    return htmlq=
        [
          {
           numn: 1,
            question: "How many types of position values are there in CSS?",
            answer: "C. 5",
            options: [
              "A. 6",
              "B. 2",
              "C. 5",
              "D. 3",
            ],
          },
          {
            numn: 2,
            question: "The default position of an HTML element.",
            answer: "A. static",
            options: [
              "A. static",
              "B. relative",
              "C. absolute",
              "D. Fixed",
            ],
          },
          {
            numn: 3,
            question: "Which of the following are the possible values of CSS float property?",
            answer: "D. All of the above",
            options: [
              "A. left or right",
              "B. inherit",
              "C. None",
              "D. All of the above"],
          },
          {
            numn: 4,
            question: "Which of the following CSS properties is used to control the layout?",
            answer: "B. display",
            options: [
              "A. layout",
              "B. display",
              "C. float",
              "D. Clear",
            ],
          },
          {
            numn: 5,
            question: "hich of the following is the right value range for opacity property?",
            answer: "B. 0.0 to 1.0",
            options: [
              "A. 0 to 5",
              "B. 0.0 to 1.0",
              "C. 0.0 to 0.5",
              "D. 0 to 10",
            ],
          },
          {
            numn: 6,
            question: "Default value of background-repeat property by the web page.",
            answer: "A. repeat",
            options: [
              "A. repeat",
              "B. repeat-x",
              "C. repeat-y",
              "D. no-repeat",
            ],
          },
          {
            numn: 7,
            question: "Which property will control the background scrolls or remains with the page?",
            answer: "B. background-attachment",
            options: [
              "A. background-tile",
              "B. background-attachment",
              "C. background-image-control",
              "D. background-attachment-control",
            ],
          },
          {
            numn: 8,
            question: "The selector that uses tag name for applying styles is known as _____________.",
            answer: "D. Both a and b",
            options: [
              "A. Type selector",
              "B. Element selector",
              "C. Universal selector",
              "D. Both a and b",
            ],
          },
          {
            numn: 9,
            question: "Which of the following symbols is used to prepend Id selectors?",
            answer: "B.  #",
            options: [
              "A.  .",
              "B.  #",
              "C.  *",
              "D.  ~",
            ],
          },
          {
            numn: 10,
            question: "Which of the following is the best practice to include CSS?",
            answer: "D. Both A and B",
            options: [
              "A. Internal CSS.",
              "B. Inline CSS.",
              "C. External CSS.",
              "D. Both A and B",
            ],
          }
        ]
  }
 if (x==2) {
   return htmlq=[
        {
          numn: 1,
          question:
            "Which of the following are the important manipulations done in a for loop?",
          answer: "A. Initialization",
          options: [
            "A. Initialization",
            "B. Incrementation",
            "C. Both A and B",
            "D. None of the above",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 2,
          question:
            "Which of the following statements is more efficient than the Else If statement?",
          answer: "C. Switch Statement",
          options: [
            "A. If Statement",
            "B. Else If Statement",
            "C. Switch Statement",
            "D. None of the above",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 3,
          question:
            "What will happen if you forget to increase/decrease the value of the variable in the while loop?",
          answer: "B. Loop will never end",
          options: [
            "A. Loop will not start",
            "B. Loop will never end",
            "C. Error",
            "D. None of the above",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 4,
          question: "The Do-While loop performs at least _______ iterations?",
          answer: "B. 1",
          options: ["A. Not necessarily an iteration", "B. 1", "C. 2", "D. Error"],
        },
        {
          numn: 5,
          question:
            "The functions in JavaScript are executed in which of the following manner?",
          answer: "A. sequence",
          options: [
            "A. sequence",
            "B. parallel",
            "C. alternate",
            "D. All of the above.",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 6,
          question: "What will happen if we call setTimeout() with a time of 0 ms?",
          answer: "B. Placed in queue.",
          options: [
            "A. Placed in stack",
            "B. Placed in queue",
            "C. Will run continuously",
            "D. None of the above",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 7,
          question:
            "________ method is used to attach an event handler to a particular element.",
          answer: "C. addEventListener()",
          options: [
            "A. addEvent()",
            "B. addListener()",
            "C. addEventListener()",
            "D. addListenerEvent()",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 8,
          question: "DOM Stands for ________.",
          answer: "A. Document Object Method.",
          options: [
            "A. Document Object Method.",
            "B. Document Oriented Method.",
            "C. Document Objects Method.",
            "D. Document Object Methods.",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 9,
          question:
            "Which of the following properties will allow you to add properties and methods to an Array object?",
          answer: "C. prototype",
          options: [
            "A. constructor",
            "B. length",
            "C. prototype",
            "D. None of the above",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 10,
          question:
            "Which of the following is the other name of multidimensional array",
          answer: "B. Array of array",
          options: [
            "A. Array within array",
            "B. Array of array",
            "C. Array inside array",
            "D. All of the above",
          ],
        },
      ];

 }
 if (x==3) {
  return htmlq=[
        {
          numn: 1,
          question: "What is the name of web search engine owned by Microsoft",
          answer: "B. Bing",
          options: ["A. Baidu", "B. Bing", "C. Yahoo!", "D. Google"],
        },
        {
          numn: 2,
          question: "W3C stands for _________",
          answer: "A. World Wide Web Consortium",
          options: [
            "A. World Wide Web Consortium",
            "B. World Wide Web Community",
            "C. World Wide Websites Consortium",
            "D. World Wide Websites Community",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 3,
          question: "Incognito mode in browsers is used for ________",
          answer: "B. Private Browsing",
          options: [
            "A. Save cookies",
            "B. Private Browsing",
            "C. Hide from an Internet service provider",
            "D. Public Browsing",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 4,
          question: "Website is a collection of  ________",
          answer: "A. Webpage",
          options: [
            "A. Webpage",
            "B. HTML Page",
            "C. Both (A) & (B)",
            "D. HTTP Page",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 5,
          question: "Which of the following is not a Web browser?",
          answer: "C. XML",
          options: ["A. Netscape Navigator", "B. NetSurf", "C. XML", "D, Opera"],
        },
        {
          numn: 6,
          question: "_______ was the first web browser to implement the omnibox.",
          answer: "D. Google Chrome",
          options: [
            "A. Mozilla FireFox",
            "B. Safari",
            "C. Lynux",
            "D. Google Chrome",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 7,
          question: "A computer with software installed to deliver web pages.",
          answer: "A. Web Server",
          options: ["A. Web Server", "B. Browser", "C. Notepad++", "D. Publiser"],
        },
        {
          numn: 8,
          question: "A program that connects you to a website",
          answer: "C. Browser",
          options: [
            "A. Notepad++",
            "B. DreamWeaver",
            "C. Browser",
            "D. Search Engine",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 9,
          question:
            "Everything that happens on the server (behind-the-scenes) to make the front-end perform as intended.",
          answer: "D. Back End",
          options: [
            "A. Front End",
            "B. Browser",
            "C. Search Engine",
            "D. Back End",
          ],
        },
        {
          numn: 10,
          question: "The name of the web site?",
          answer: "D. Domain",
          options: ["A. Index", "B. Resource", "C. Home", "D. Domain"],
        },
      ];
 }


}
qchage(0);










